[
  {
    "question": "پایتخت فرانسه کدام است؟",
    "options": [
      "برلین",
      "پاریس",
      "رم",
      "مدرید"
    ],
    "answer": "پاریس"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 2 چند می‌شود؟",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "سریع‌ترین حیوان؟",
    "options": [
      "یوزپلنگ",
      "ببر",
      "شیر",
      "فیل"
    ],
    "answer": "یوزپلنگ"
  },
  {
    "question": "HTML چیست؟",
    "options": [
      "ساختار صفحه",
      "سبک‌دهی",
      "پایگاه داده",
      "سیستم‌عامل"
    ],
    "answer": "ساختار صفحه"
  },
  {
    "question": "CSS برای چیست؟",
    "options": [
      "ساختار",
      "سرعت",
      "زیباسازی",
      "امنیت"
    ],
    "answer": "زیباسازی"
  },
  {
    "question": "سازنده اپل؟",
    "options": [
      "بیل گیتس",
      "استیو جابز",
      "ایلان ماسک",
      "لری پیج"
    ],
    "answer": "استیو جابز"
  },
  {
    "question": "رنگ آسمان؟",
    "options": [
      "قرمز",
      "آبی",
      "سبز",
      "سیاه"
    ],
    "answer": "آبی"
  },
  {
    "question": "بزرگ‌ترین قاره؟",
    "options": [
      "آسیا",
      "اروپا",
      "آمریکا",
      "استرالیا"
    ],
    "answer": "آسیا"
  },
  {
    "question": "پرچم ایران چند رنگ دارد؟",
    "options": [
      "۱",
      "۲",
      "۳",
      "۴"
    ],
    "answer": "۳"
  },
  {
    "question": "JS چیست؟",
    "options": [
      "زبان برنامه‌نویسی",
      "اپلیکیشن",
      "سخت‌افزار",
      "درایور"
    ],
    "answer": "زبان برنامه‌نویسی"
  }
]